<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-07-30T04:46:37-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Degreeless.marketing</title><subtitle>Marketing for self-learners.</subtitle><author><name>Lukas Murdock</name></author><entry><title type="html">The Greatest Salesman In the World - The Scroll Marked I</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/bookreview/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-the-scroll-marked-i" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Greatest Salesman In the World - The Scroll Marked I" /><published>2018-11-11T19:46:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-11-11T19:46:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/bookreview/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-the-scroll-marked-i</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/bookreview/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-the-scroll-marked-i">&lt;p&gt;You’re viewing Part i&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are in sales or simply want to read a positive message about spirit, perseverance, and success…I encourage you to read &lt;em&gt;The Greatest Salesman in the World&lt;/em&gt; written by OG Mandino. &lt;em&gt;I read this book for the first time 20 years ago and to this day it is one of my Top 5 books&lt;/em&gt;. It’s a very quick read and I’ve re-read the book each year of my life using the affirmations to guide my journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the coming days/weeks I will share a brief summary of each Scroll (aka affirmation).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Scroll Marked I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Today I begin a new life. Failure is mankind’s inability to reach his/her goals in life, whatever they may be. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Good habits are the key to all success. Bad habits are the unlocked door to failure.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;I will form good habits and I will become their slave.&lt;/em&gt; Each scroll contains a principle which will drive a bad habit from my life and replace it with one which will bring me closer to success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will read each scroll for 30 days in this prescribed manner, before I proceed to the next scroll. First, I will read the words in silence when I arise. Then, I will read the words in silence after I have partaken of my midday meal. Last, I will read the words again just before I retire at day’s end, and most important, on this occasion I will read the words aloud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Herein lies the hidden secret of all mankind’s accomplishments. &lt;em&gt;As I repeat the words daily they will soon become a part of my active mind, but more important, for when an act become easy through constant repetition it becomes a pleasure to perform and if it is a pleasure to perform it is mankind’s nature to perform it often.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;When I perform it often it becomes a habit and I become its slave and since it is a good habit this is my will&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Today I begin a new life. And I make a solemn oath to myself that nothing will slow my new life’s growth.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a link to obtain this wonderful read if you are interested. &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Greatest-Salesman-World-Og-Mandino/dp/055327757X&quot;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/Greatest-Salesman-World-Og-Mandino/dp/055327757X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this book provides you with guidance for your journey.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Lukas Murdock</name></author><category term="bookreview" /><summary type="html">You’re viewing Part i</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/weblogo.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/weblogo.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>